{
    "questions": [
        {"question" : "On the document object, what function will target a specific id?",
        "answer" : "getElementById",
        "description" : "getElementById targets a specific id on a page. In jQuery, $('#idName') is used.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/js/js_intro.asp",
        "about" : "getElementById",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "You can display data in the console using the what method.",
        "answer" : "console.log",
        "description" : "The console.log method allows you to display data in the console.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/js/js_output.asp",
        "about" : "console.log",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "In JavaScript, what would 3 * (5 + 2)?",
        "answer" : "21",
        "description" : "JavaScript follows the order of operations.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/js/js_syntax.asp",
        "about" : "assignment operator",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "To create a multi-line comment in JavaScript, start with what?",
        "answer" : "/*",
        "description" : "Multi-line comments start with /* and end with */.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/js/js_comments.asp",
        "about" : "JavaScript Comments",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "The modulus operator shows you what is left over from an arthimetic operation. What is the symbol?",
        "answer" : "%",
        "description" : "The modulus operator shows what is left over from an arthimetic operation. One use of it can determine if a number is even or odd.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/js/js_operators.asp",
        "about" : "Modulus",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "How do you take a number to some power? Using the Math object, what is the function?",
        "answer" : "pow",
        "description" : "Math.pow will take a number to some power.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/jsref/jsref_pow.asp",
        "about" : "Math.pow",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "How do you find a square root of some number? Using the Math object, what is the function?",
        "answer" : "sqrt",
        "description" : "Math.sqrt will give you the square root of a number.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com",
        "about" : "Math.sqrt",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "Math.random will return a number between 0 and what?",
        "answer" : "1",
        "description" : "Math.random returns a number between 0 and 1, such as .2.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/jsref/jsref_random.asp",
        "about" : "Math.random",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "How do you force a number to round down? Using the Math object, what is the function?",
        "answer" : "floor",
        "description" : "Math.floor will round a number down. An example is Math.floor(4.75) will return 4.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/jsref/jsref_floor.asp",
        "about" : "Math.floor",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "How do you force a number to round up? Using the Math object, what is the function?",
        "answer" : "ceil",
        "description" : "Math.ceil will round a number up. An example is Math.ceil(8.1) will return 9.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/jsref/jsref_ceil.asp",
        "about" : "Math.ceil",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "What type is true?",
        "answer" : "boolean",
        "description" : "Both true and false are booleans. An example is (2 < 9) would return true.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/js/js_booleans.asp",
        "about" : "boolean",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "What function makes a string uppercase?",
        "answer" : "toUppercase",
        "description" : "toUppercase is used to make a string uppercase.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/jsref/jsref_touppercase.asp",
        "about" : "toUppercase",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "What function removes and returns the last element in an array?",
        "answer" : "pop",
        "description" : "pop removes and returns the last element in an array.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/jsref/jsref_pop.asp",
        "about" : "pop",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "What function adds an element to the end of an array?",
        "answer" : "push",
        "description" : "push adds an element to the end of an array.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/jsref/jsref_push.asp",
        "about" : "push",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "What function removes and returns the first element of an array?",
        "answer" : "shift",
        "description" : "shift removes and returns the first element of an array.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/jsref/jsref_shift.asp",
        "about" : "shift",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "What function adds an element to the beginning of an array?",
        "answer" : "unshift",
        "description" : "unshift adds an element to the beginning of an array.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/jsref/jsref_unshift.asp",
        "about" : "unshift",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "What function allows you to concatenate two arrays together?",
        "answer" : "concat",
        "description" : "concat allows you to concatenate two arrays together.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/jsref/jsref_concat_array.asp",
        "about" : "concat",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "What function allows you to return a copy of a portion of an array?",
        "answer" : "slice",
        "description" : "slice allows you to return a copy of a portion of an array.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/jsref/jsref_slice_array.asp",
        "about" : "slice",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "What function allows you to alter an array by adding or removing elements?",
        "answer" : "splice",
        "description" : ".splice allows you to alter an array by adding or removing elements.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/jsref/jsref_splice.asp",
        "about" : "splice",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "What function allows you to reverse an array?",
        "answer" : "reverse",
        "description" : ".reverse allows you to reverse an array.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/jsref/jsref_reverse.asp",
        "about" : "reverse",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "What function allows you to sort the elements in an array?",
        "answer" : "sort",
        "description" : "sort allows you to sort the elements in an array.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/jsref/jsref_sort.asp",
        "about" : "sort",
        "type": "javascript"
        },
        {"question" : "What function allows you to take an array and combine the elements together as a string?",
        "answer" : "join",
        "description" : "join allows you to take an array and join the elements together as a string.",
        "link" : "http://www.w3schools.com/jsref/jsref_join.asp",
        "about" : "join",
        "type": "javascript"
        }
    ]
}